let quiz = [
    {
        question: "Who killed Severus Snape",
        option: [
            "Bellatrix Lestrange",
            " Nagini",
            "He-Who-Must-Not-Be-Named",
            "Lucius Malfoy",
        ],
        answer: 3,
    },
    {
        question: "At the first meeting of the Duelling Club, Draco Malfoy summoned what animal with the spell 'Serpensortia'?",
        option: [
            "Frog",
            "Snake",
            "Dragon",
            "Bear",
        ],
        answer: 2,
    },
    {
        question: "What spell did Harry use to kill Lord Voldemort?",
        option: [
            "Expelliarmus",
            "Expecto Patronum",
            "Avada Kedavra",
            "Accio",
        ],
        answer: 1,
    },
    {
        question:
            "Wit beyond measure is man's greatest treasure' is the motto of which house?",
        option: [
            "Gryffindor",
            "Hufflepuff",
            "Ravenclaw",
            "Slytherin",
        ],
        answer: 3,
    },
    {
        question:
        "What does the scar on Harryâ€™s head look like?",
        option: [
            "A broomstick",
            "A lighthing bolt",
            "An owl",
            "The moon",
        ],
        answer: 2,
    },
    {
        question: "Who saved a centaur from being strangled by Professor Umbridge in the Forbidden Forest?",
        option: ["Grawp", "Hagrid", "Buckbeak", "Luna"],
        answer: 1,
    },
    {
        question: "Which element is associated with Hufflepuff?",
        option: [
            "Fire",
            "Earth",
            "Air",
            "Water",
        ],
        answer: 2,
    },
    {
        question:
            "Cedric Diggory faced what breed of dragon in the Triwizard Tournament?",
        option: ["Swedish Short-Snout", "Peruvian Vipertooth", "Common Welsh Green", "Norwegian Ridgeback"],
        answer: 1,
    },
    {
        question: "Select the centaurs named in the Harry Potter books",
        option: ["Firenze", "Alderman", "Lurius", "Falco"],
        answer: 1,
    },
    {
        question: "Albus Dumbledore destroyed which Horcrux?",
        option: ["Slytherin's locket", "Nagini", "Hufflepuff's cup", "Marvolo Gaunt's ring"],
        answer: 4,
    },
];
